<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>kenwoo.me</title>
    <link>http://kenwoo.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on kenwoo.me</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 18:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://kenwoo.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Busted Knee: Lesson One</title>
      <link>http://kenwoo.me/blog/busted-knee-lesson-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 18:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kenwoo.me/blog/busted-knee-lesson-one/</guid>
      <description>On March 29, 2018, 1:15 AM, I had my MRI. It&amp;rsquo;s been just under 4 months since the original injury. Rehab in the gym had been going great. I was not only maintaining strength, I was getting stronger than before. And only a week ago, I tried to play some very recreational indoor volleyball to tested my leg out. I was a friggin rock-star. Okay not really, I took it easy but was able to jump confidently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Busted Knee</title>
      <link>http://kenwoo.me/blog/busted-knee/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 16:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kenwoo.me/blog/busted-knee/</guid>
      <description>In the beginning of December 2017, I dislocated my right knee when pushing off to move forward during a beach volleyball game.
What a drag.
After a few visits to a physiotherapist and a sport medicine doctor, and eventually getting an MRI, it turns out I have a torn ACL. I am told that I am a good candidate for ACL reconstructive surgery. Either that or I quit any sport that could cause dislocation of the knee, further damaging adjacent structures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10% Happier</title>
      <link>http://kenwoo.me/blog/10-happier/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kenwoo.me/blog/10-happier/</guid>
      <description>I recently went on a life-changing journey that I want to share.
It all started with the book The Inner Game of Tennis by Timothy Gallwey, which introduced me to a few ideas:
 learn to observe a result without emotional attachment attempting to consciously control every movement will result in stunted long-term skill development it is through attempting to micro-manage your movements during crunch time that causes your body to tense up resulting in the dreaded &amp;ldquo;choke&amp;rdquo;  It is not uncommon for people to overthink their movements in training or sport.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code</title>
      <link>http://kenwoo.me/code/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kenwoo.me/code/</guid>
      <description>Countdown until World Domination After receiving ACL surgery for my right knee, I was told to aim for one whole year of rehabilitation and gradual return to world domination sport.
Crossing out days on a calendar is so last decade, so I made this page to help me keep track of when it is time to profit again.
Source Code on Github
MPT Log Generator When I was training a lot, my coach wanted me to keep a daily journal of what I did each session on Google Docs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>http://kenwoo.me/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kenwoo.me/home/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Kenny Woo. Welcome to my humble abode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating the Small Successes</title>
      <link>http://kenwoo.me/blog/celebrating-the-small-successes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kenwoo.me/blog/celebrating-the-small-successes/</guid>
      <description>The lofty goals I set for myself seem to be the most fun to achieve. However, in the midst of the journey, I tend to focus too much on what I have yet to achieve, rather than what I have achieved so far.
I recently began to shift my focus to acknowledging and celebrating the small successes. And why the heck not? Even the seemingly tiniest of achievements are quite massive in their own right.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>